typewolf.com 2016-03-20

# Privacy → Typewolf

### Privacy Policy

Typewolf is owned and operated by [Jeremiah Shoaf Design LLC](http://www.jeremiahshoaf.com/).

##### Our Commitment to Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.

_Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this website only. If you follow links to other websites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites._

##### The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Typewolf website. When you submit a site to us or subscribe to our mailing list we collect the following personal information from you:

Email address

##### The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself when submitting a site only for the purposes of reviewing sites to add to the gallery. We do not share this information with outside parties.

We use email addresses submitted on the mailing list form to send email updates. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. You can unsubscribe from the mailing list at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

##### Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

##### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Typewolf may change its privacy policy from time to time, and in Typewolf’s sole discretion. Typewolf encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its privacy policy.

##### How to Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please email us at jeremiah@typewolf.com.

Our mailing address is:  
Jeremiah Shoaf Design LLC  
PO Box 746524  
Arvada, CO 80006  

### Disclosure

Some of the external links on Typewolf are affiliate links. If a visitor clicks a link and makes a purchase, Typewolf may receive a commission.
